[Meet Yourself]
[Episode 27]
[Tomb of Chen Nanxing]
Nanxing,
Hongdou comes from afar to see you.
Please bless her success in work
and peace in life.
As long as she can get some rest.
Don't bother to bless me.
I won't disturb you two anymore.
Let's go.
Right.
Don't be in a hurry.
We are waiting for you in the parking lot.
See?
Full of rewards.
What you told me to do,
I did most of them.
I made friends.
I tasted a lot of good food.
I had a lot of fun.
I also found the feeling of being a child.
How does that feel?
It's just...
I don't know.
Probably, the feeling
closest to happiness.
I'll show you the photos.
♫ Listen to the rain
falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops on the roof
fall into the eyes secretly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
Poplar in the Water.
Do you still remember?
And this one.
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
Is he handsome?
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
Our agreement is always valid.
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
I have to go now.
Take care of yourselves.
All right.
You should go now.
Don't let the car wait.
Be safe.
Text me when you get back.
Please say hello to your parents for me.
Take care.
This is a return, not trash.
It is to be sold again.
Why do you throw it like that?
This is just tea.
Can tea be thrown like that?
Won't the tea leaves be broken?
Won't the teapot be deflated?
What are you doing?
I just touched you.
You almost kicked him.
If you kick someone, I need to compensate.
Do you know how much loan our family has?
Can I put you in a mortgage?
Well, you're in a bad mood?
Hearing me talking like that?
I am in a bad mood too.
No dinner tonight.
Getting the 14th place in the exam,
you dare to talk back to your mother.
If you get into Tsinghua or Peking University,
the whole family has to welcome you
on their knees, right?
What attitude you have!
You call this a good attitude?
Fine.
Let's talk about this today.
Don't you know what state you are in at school?
[Yunmiao Village Service Station]
Who is the thief in the end?
You are the thief!
You stole the land!
You occupied such a large piece!
Uncle, it's enough.
Go measure.
But, uncle... Do it!
Let Huang take the lead to measure.
Can we stop?
Did the ridging affect your field?
Give me back my corn!
No.
Let's not do it!
Give me back my corn!
Stop it!
Uncles.
We can't deal with it by talking, can we?
Come.
Smash.
Look what you did to me last time.
It is still not recovered.
Just smash it.
Let your anger out.
Don't do it all year round,
once when sowing the seeds,
once during the harvest.
I'm really tired.
Smash, smash here.
Come on, with this.
Smash with this.
Come on, smash.
Yao.
Don't.
Why doesn't she come?
Hasn't she got in the taxi?
Yes.
How's your sauce?
It's ready.
The fat has been stewed.
That's good.
Or I will go to the entrance of
the housing estate to get her.
Then you should go.
You can't sit still at home anyway.
Like there is a nail in your ass.
She is back!
You can cook the noodles!
Dou, you're back.
Dad!
The apron is dirty.
What's in the stew?
Smells good.
My turn!
You are overindulged.
Not coming back.
Your waist is thick again.
Get lost.
Wash your hands!
Where is the luggage I sent back?
It's in your room.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Come on!
Your mom made your favorite,
noodles with soybean paste.
Here are the noodles!
Come.
The sugar garlic you asked for.
Why didn't you eat?
Your dad said to wait for you.
Dumplings for leaving, noodles for coming back.
Your mom is worried that
you've eaten on the road.
Come.
Eat before they get cold.
I tell you what.
I knew that you must have made
delicious food for me.
So I didn't eat anything.
This is what I call smart.
How is it? Is it salty?
Especially delicious.
Number one in the world.
How are Nanxing's parents?
They are all right.
Well.
They asked me to say hello for them to you.
Don't sigh.
How's the new home coming along?
Almost done.
The house has been cleaned.
Formaldehyde has also been tested.
The air quality has met the standard.
Recently, your mom and I have already moved
a lot of things over there.
We don't know how to do with the stuff
in your room.
To throw or to keep.
You can clean up when you come back.
What's wrong with my room?
See for yourself.
Magazine 20 years ago.
You still have it.
Why do you want to keep it?
Remembrance.
I think you can live together with
Grandma Liu next building.
Keeping everything.
Picking up junk to home every day.
She never listens to her son or daughter-in-law.
There is no place to put your feet
on since the pile of junk at home.
Your mom likes to talk exaggeratedly.
I don't see much stuff.
Just one cabinet.
It's not too much.
Didn't you say that the other day?
Do we need to throw the cabinet of junk?
You've become a good person now.
When did I say that's junk?
I said they were old items.
Junk. Items.
You didn't hear clearly.
Okay, next time you talk, I'll record it.
I didn't say that anyway.
This is called selective memory loss.
Remember if he wants to.
If he doesn't want to remember,
the matter doesn't exist.
Sister, auntie said you're back.
My mom and I will go to your house in two days.
Remember to buy me cherries in advance.
[Xie Zhiyao: Have you seen her parents?
Xu Hongdou: No. Need to take the bus now.]
[Xie Zhiyao: Take care.
Xu Hongdou: Thanks!]
[What are you doing...]
[Moments: My mom's hand-made noodles
are the best in the universe.]
[Mai: Leave the bowl to me when you finish.]
[Reply to Mai: You're really a spider,
always online...]
Yang Zhinan is way out of line!
We just get together.
It was his first birthday.
I made a point of asking him what day it is.
It was easy to know that I want to
buy him a gift and celebrate it together.
At five o'clock today, I
went to pick up the cake.
I also got my hair styled for him.
I called him to see if he was off work.
He said to me he didn't work today.
He asked for leave and went home.
He went home?
I asked him why he had gone home.
He said he took time off to go home
for his birthday.
He said it was okay.
I could give him the birthday gift tomorrow.
I'm so angry.
I want to break up with him!
Wait a minute, Qin.
That boy, he may not
have been in love before.
He is an honest man.
He doesn't know about this.
How does he not know?
Doesn't he want to be with me every day?
Won't you get bored soon if you
get together every day?
Will he get bored?
Will he get bored with me?
Not him.
I mean... You can't hang
out with him every day.
People get tired no matter
how beautiful you are.
When you're in love, you
need to give him space.
Space?
Why does love need space?
I've given him enough space.
I didn't ask him to call me during work time.
He just needs to send me location
every half hour.
Qin, I don't want to
teach you how to do it.
Yang Guanjun, watch your mouth.
In terms of seniority, I am your sister-in-law
Jiabao and Guobao call you sister.
You're my sister-in-law?
If you agree with me,
I can call you brother.
But if you disagree, I
am your sister-in-law.
That's not what I mean.
I'm just saying, I've been there.
If you guys hang out every
day, you'll get bored very soon.
Do you know that?
He will get bored.
Will he?
Oh my god, Uncle Yao, do you hear that?
Yes, I do.
He will get bored!
What's wrong with him?
He goes too far!
Yang Zhinan goes too far.
What space does he need?
What space does love need?
Shouldn't you and the person you like
spend every second of your life together?
Right?
Qin looks so gorgeous today.
She also bought a cake.
But Yang Zhinan came home.
If a guy has a girlfriend, won't
he celebrate his birthday with her?
Do you know what it means?
What does it mean?
It means he doesn't care much about you.
Yang Zhinan!
I want to break up with him.
Break up.
Right now.
Call him.
Say goodbye to him.
He goes too far.
Qin.
Don't call him.
Yang Guanjun, you stay right there.
You're not going to change my mind.
Yang Zhinan.
I give you space.
Let's break up!
I don't have a boyfriend anymore.
Qin.
Listen to me.
Let's not shed tears for love.
You should concentrate on your career.
Do you understand?
I don't even have a career.
Xie Zhiyao.
Why do you fan the flames?
In the blink of an eye, Qin
had become single again.
If you are not on her side to support her,
I won't let you get away with this.
You're jealous that she has a boyfriend
when you're single.
Right?
Yang Guanjun.
Don't you dare talk to Uncle Yao like this.
Only Uncle Yao in the world is on my side.
Yes.
I am always on your side.
Uncle Yao.
Why don't you marry me?
Great, look at what you've done.
What's wrong? Is it the fish bone?
Karma is real.
Uncle Yao.
It's really stuck!
Don't eat the cake!
Go to the hospital!
Go.
Uncle Yao, don't cough.
I am scared.
Don't swallow saliva.
Hang in there.
Fortunately, it's not very deep.
It just stuck to the tonsils.
Your tonsils look so beautiful.
Very good.
It's out.
It's been a long time since I saw
someone swallow such a big fish bone.
How did that happen?
I don't know.
Every day there are people like you
coming here for emergency care.
You must be careful while eating fish.
You're smart.
You chose to come to the hospital.
Many people drink vinegar, swallow rice,
making the fish bone get deeper.
It'll be dangerous if it cuts the esophagus.
Just a moment.
I'll take a picture.
Doesn't your girlfriend come with you?
You were here accompanying a girl
for infusion, weren't you?
Thank god, it's okay.
You scared the hell out of me.
Let's go.
Qin.
When I was a child, a fish
bone also lodged in my throat,
which was bigger than his.
This big.
Really?
At that time, I was scared to death.
You must be careful while eating fish later.
You just let him eat the cake.
The doctor said, no food.
I didn't know that he can't even eat a cake.
[Moments: A huge fish bone
got stuck in my tonsil.] You know it now.
♫ I've been alone into the unknown ♫
♫ Can't navigate through the dark ♫
♫ I'm searching for a meadow of mine ♫
♫ Till you came in with the breeze ♫
♫ Feeling a rush out of me,
spills my heart into the field ♫
♫ I know it, I will be yours ♫
♫ Would you ask for any horse ♫
♫ But this one inside your heart ♫
She didn't even give me a like.
I accompanied you to the infusion.
A fish bone stuck in the throat?
[Mai: You're my role model!]
♫ Spills my heart into the field ♫
♫ I know it, I will be yours ♫
♫ Would you ask for any horse ♫
♫ But this one inside your heart ♫
Dou, wake up for breakfast.
Okay.
Hurry up.
♫ I'll give you the saddle of mine ♫
♫ You ask me if the wind could sing ♫
♫ We close our eyes ♫
You have a headache?
No.
You should eat well.
Or you have no energy.
People need the energy to get sad.
Well, why do you think I am sad?
What are you talking about, grandma?
I'll eat it later.
Grandma.
She doesn't send me messages.
I can't text her on my initiative.
Why can't you send her messages first?
You have a bad cell phone signal?
I am serious.
Here is the thing.
The initiative is not in my hands.
Before she left,
I told her.
What did you say?
I said...
I like her.
I won't talk about it anymore
if you act like this.
Say it.
You like her, and?
Nothing else.
I told her how I feel and that's it.
Well... She said... No more contact?
Of course not.
She just said to keep in touch.
We are still friends.
That's it.
You told her everything, and now you are shy.
Don't be shy.
Take the initiative.
Maybe it works out and you will have
an online relationship.
Grandma.
She doesn't want an online relationship
or a long-distance relationship.
Then you should go to find her often.
Fly from Yunnan to Beijing.
From Beijing to Yunnan.
I have money.
I've saved money for you.
You've saved money for me?
How much have you saved?
Wait a minute.
Look.
What...
I was going to give you the money
if things don't work out for you here.
You can go back to Beijing then.
Or if you get married, this can be
the start-up fund for your family.
Of course, it's not enough
to buy a house or land.
But it can be the emergency fund.
I think...
Hongdou's leaving,
is good for both of you.
Young people like you
are having "fast-food affection".
Once she leaves, you become calm down.
If you're thinking of each other,
then think about the way forward.
What's your plan?
Don't be in a hurry.
Me and your grandpa.
We started with nothing.
We spend a lifetime to understand a truth.
That is.
You fight for what you want.
Don't wait for someone else to give.
Cheer up.
Don't be downcast.
Understand?
Understood.
Then you should eat.
Grandma, is this bankbook for me?
You can have it when you buy a ticket.
But I am still curious.
How did you save so much money?
I just... called your dad constantly,
saying I had a headache or a sore butt.
I asked him for money.
And I saved it for you.
I'll take a call.
It's from Huang.
Hello, Huang?
Hello, Xie?
Shaohua Bookstore's team will come in five days.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am sure.
Coming for a meeting.
Okay, I'll be right over.
Grandma, I have to go to the village council
for a meeting.
You can't eat again.
Take it and eat it on the way.
Okay.
Can I have that one?
Thank you, grandma.
I'm off.
When I was in Yunmiao Village,
I got up before dawn and went to that town
to eat rice noodles in a small pot
from the food market.
A slacker like you can get up early?
Someone called me.
Xie Zhiyao's home is just one lane
away from the house where I lived.
I can see their yard from my window.
He got up early.
Then he took small stones to smash my window.
You know what?
Only local people know where to find
that kind of bistro.
You're talking about the young man
who came home to start his own business, right?
That's him. He's very nice.
How old is he?
In his 30s.
I think he is quite a gentleman.
Why is he still single?
He hasn't met the right girl?
The last time he was in a relationship
was still in college.
That was more than ten years ago.
Could it be there is something wrong
with his...
Mom.
What's so embarrassing about it?
He just haven't met the right girl.
No one would think about physical defects.
Everyone would think about this way.
What else could it be?
He sets the bar too high.
Your daughter doesn't have a boyfriend.
Is there something wrong with me too?
Of course, you have no problem with that.
Now it's normal for girls to marry late.
Mom, you're having a double standard.
Of course.
I raise you, I love you. Any problem?
You're just too far away from each other.
Just eat.
I'll take you out after breakfast.
I don't go fishing with dad.
Who said to go fishing?
Let's go pick peaches, okay?
Peach picking.
Eat.
The peaches Hongdou picked are very good.
One has to weigh 250 g, right?
It's sweet.
What is it?
Hope to hear good news from you.
What good news?
She is talking about the bookstore.
Grandma, look here.
This one is particularly good.
Let me have a look.
You took such an ugly picture of me!
So ugly!
You're cute. You don't understand!
What? Cute?
I sent it.
I sent it over.
You want to taste my fist?
Don't.
I'll send a box to Ms. Xie.
It hurts.
I need to go.
Come, eat peaches.
Sweet.
So sweet.
You sent more than 100 kg over?
How much does this express cost?
It's a pity.
She is a good girl.
Unfortunately, she is not used to living here.
Did you see Yao the other day?
He was angry for a while.
He didn't talk for a while.
He was like a deflated balloon, out of spirits.
He came here this morning.
He is pretty good.
He is in good spirits, smiling all the time.
So men and women are not the same.
If a man breaks up, he won't be
brokenhearted for more than a week.
Even Mr. Xie is like this.
I am disappointed in men.
You are right.
Men forget quickly.
Look at Baoping.
She didn't get married after her husband
was gone for years.
Right.
And Mr. Crow.
After his wife was gone for less than 100 days,
he went to a matchmaker to get him a new one.
Shameless!
That old man is shameless.
Shameless.
But, Chuchu, Yue, don't despair.
There are still good men.
Like Guanjun.
Guanjun is really good.
Don't blow your own horn.
You will know when similar things happen.
You're right.
Sweet?
Sweet.
Open your mouth.
Sweet?
Sweet.
Don't look at me.
Try one.
Sweet.
Sister,
you asked Nana for those bottles
of wine, and those cans and jars.
Why do you need them?
I want to do magic.
Don't beat around the bush.
Don't throw the peach kernel
after you eat the peach.
Keep it for me.
What do you need it for?
It's all about life.
Understand?
Come here.
Your hair is too long.
I'll cut it for you.
You can also cut hair?
Of course.
My daughter's hair is cut by me.
That's great.
You know what?
The barbershop here is too expensive.
It costs several dozen yuan for a haircut.
In return, you have to sing a song for me.
Sure.
What song do you want to hear?
The Wind.
Blow it away.
Blow it away, in my
face... I'll get the guitar.
Jiahui!
♫ The journey ♫
Hello.
♫ One step to the stars ♫
This is our special Sugar Peach.
♫ One step to the rainbow ♫
Please have a try.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
♫ Miss and embrace ♫
♫ In the world ♫
♫ Where there is a breeze ♫
Hello.
This is our special Sugar Peach.
Please try it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Please enjoy.
♫ In the street with rain or sunshine ♫
You guys look so unnatural.
It's not real.
Come on, look at each other.
Looking at each other.
And you should smile.
It's like this peach is very tasty.
Okay, that's it.
3, 2, 1.
♫ Sometimes I need a beautiful smile ♫
Good.
Off you go.
♫ Although the seasons go by ♫
Why do I feel we have been used like tools?
It's okay.
I am worried that he will go back to Beijing
for Xu Hongdou on impulse.
♫ Make a little wish and pray ♫
I don't want to eat.
♫ Maybe it will work out the way
I want it to ♫
♫ Sometimes I need a beautiful smile ♫
♫ Although the seasons go by ♫
♫ Love as a teenager ♫
♫ Sometimes I find I fall in love ♫
Let's take a look at the gifts
your auntie prepared.
♫ Make a little wish and pray ♫
♫ Maybe it will work out ♫
Tiger head shoes?
This is made by a grandma in Yunnan.
She wouldn't take the money.
Every stitch is her heart.
If our grandma was still alive,
she should also make tiger head shoes
for my baby.
There is our grandma's smell on her body.
Smell it.
It's true.
It's the smell of boiled peanuts.
Not the smell of toast?
It's boiled peanuts.
Wipe it off quickly.
If our mom sees this, she would
think I have done something to you.
I'm fine. I'm pregnant.
I'm just sensitive.
Kexin.
How is your husband treating you?
Not bad.
We are both quite lazy.
His mother spoiled him. He knows nothing.
My mom spoiled me and I can't do anything.
Two childish adults.
We don't frown upon each other.
Fortune favors fools.
Sister.
I didn't find a perfect guy.
You have to be careful to find a good one.
How good does it have to be?
First, he has to be handsome.
He can make money.
And then?
His family spirit should be good.
His parents have to be reasonable.
He can afford a house in Beijing.
At the very least, he should have
a Beijing household registration.
If he is not from Beijing?
Shanghai is fine too.
What about Yunnan?
Yunnan?
Yunnan is...
You fell in love with someone from Yunnan?
Do you have a one-night stand in Yunnan?
What are you talking about?
Don't let your mom and my mom hear it.
Who do you like?
You know what?
If you are not pregnant, I'll beat you.
What are you talking about?
Baby.
Mom is so scared.
Why are you getting mad?
You are the most annoying.
Get down to business.
Have you found your new job yet?
New job?
Auntie said
you're tired of the hotel you worked
for ten years in Beijing,
and want to find a new one.
How's it going?
Slow down.
Mom.
Is there anything I can help?
Just wait and eat.
Mom.
Mom, mom.
What are you doing?
Say what you want.
How did you know I resigned?
Gang from auntie Sun is going to visit Beijing.
She called your hotel, to
see if she can get a discount
by mentioning your name.
But they told her Manager Xu resigned.
Xu Hongdou.
Now you should know you can't hide anything.
From childhood to adulthood,
whenever you lie, you will be exposed, right?
You know I resigned.
Why didn't you ask?
I see you're out there, having a good time.
What should I ask?
We can talk about it when you come back.
You didn't ask about it when I got back.
Then tell me.
It's nothing really.
You told me when I was a child
that the slow need to start early.
I can't fly anymore.
I'm tired.
I just want to take a break.
It's okay not to fly.
It's good to fly back to the nest.
Our family is counting on Xu
Hongmi, the little cash catcher,
to catch money for us.
Just like the nest of swallows under the eaves
of your grandma's house.
Mom.
I'm telling you seriously.
Okay.
Let's talk seriously.
What's your plan?
Your dad and your sister,
want you to go to Shanghai.
I actually have an HR friend,
telling me their hotel's training
department is recruiting.
The job is quite suitable for me.
A normal working hour job.
No need for a 24-hour standby.
That's good.
As long as you like it.
You don't have to worry about me and your dad.
We have some savings.
We don't spend much either.
And again, there is your sister.
As long as you can feed
yourself, I won't worry about you.
Don't be so stressed.
But I don't want to be much worse than my sis.
Why do you always compare with her?
I am not.
It's just from childhood to adulthood,
you always compare me with her.
That's my fault.
I shouldn't have done this.
We are wrong.
I apologize to you.
I was wrong.
Mom, you're so quick to admit you're wrong.
It is a pre-emptive strike.
I don't even know what to say.
You don't know what to say,
just don't say anything.
Wait for the dumplings.
No more water, okay?
Leave it to me, okay?
These people are really bad.
This is nice.
I am done.
It's my turn.
Okay.
I'll give you a massage.
How's it?
Wow, the strength.
[Xie Zhiyao: How many peaches do you pick?
Why don't you reply after coming back home?]
What's going on?
Who is it?
Hongdou is calling.
Answer it.
Stupid boy.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Hello, are you busy?
Why didn't you answer my call just now?
I was with my grandma just now.
I went upstairs.
What are you doing?
I am packing up my books.
I am going to move these days.
I didn't have time to reply this afternoon.
My aunt brought my cousin over here.
It was noisy.
Everyone was making dumplings.
My cousin is pregnant for several months.
I was playing with her.
No wonder.
In fact, if you call me this
afternoon, I can't pick it up either.
I was having a meeting about
the bookstore in the village.
Any progress?
The team will officially come to visit
in a few days,
negotiating the reception.
I'll cooperate with the village.
About the guesthouse.
Some guys will come to see the place
in a few days.
Not easy to sell?
Not easy.
The guy who wants to take
it, offers a very low price.
He just wants a steal.
The previous owner is in want of money.
The price has been dropping again and again.
I see.
Let's not talk about that.
It's all about annoyance.
The noodles your mother
made... How's your throat?
Why didn't you give me a like
since you've seen it?
When I saw it, you've
posted it for eleven hours.
Is it appropriate to give a like for
things like that?
It doesn't matter to me.
♫ The journey ♫
♫ One step to the stars ♫
You didn't give me a like either.
When I saw it, it's also
been more than ten hours.
When you posted it,
I went to the hospital.
♫ Miss and embrace ♫
Okay.
♫ In the world ♫
So... ♫ Where there is a breeze ♫
are we good?
♫ Where the heart is hidden ♫
So... keep in touch?
♫ Fill whose dreams ♫
♫ In the street with rain ♫
Why are you laughing?
♫ or sunshine ♫
Can't I laugh when I am happy?
Aren't you happy to be home?
♫ The time of walking and walking far ♫
♫ Before saying goodbye ♫
I can't talk to you right now.
Have a good rest. Good night.
Sure.
That's it.
Good night.
♫ Although the seasons go by ♫
♫ Love as a teenager ♫
♫ Sometimes I find I fall in love ♫
♫ Make a little wish and pray ♫
What are you doing?
Your mom is eavesdropping.
Xu Jianguo!
You...
♫ Listen to the rain
falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops on the roof
fall into the eyes secretly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ Go to a windy place to meet you ♫